<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Baughurst Scout and Guide Group]]></title>
  <link href="http://baughurstsgg.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://baughurstsgg.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-12-12T17:41:53+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://baughurstsgg.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Baughurst Scout and Guide Group]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cubs football success]]></title>
    <link href="http://baughurstsgg.github.com/blog/2012/03/25/cubs-football-success/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-25T12:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://baughurstsgg.github.com/blog/2012/03/25/cubs-football-success</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Baughurst was representing Silchester at the annual event held in Southampton, which is open to all Scout Districts in Hampshire, after having won the District competition where they had played against teams from Headley, Bramley and Tadley. This is the first time that Baughurst Cub Scouts have represented Silchester at this event.</p>

<p>On the day 18 teams took part in the Competition, which is now in its 28th year, and consists of 2 trophies; the Main Cup, which is played on a league basis with the top team in each league going through to the Final stages, and the Plate Trophy, a knock out competition for teams who did not win their league.</p>

<p>The event itself is probably best summed up by two emails received.
The first from Graham Brooks  &#8220;What a Day! On Sunday Baughurst Cub Scouts won Hampshire Counties Scout Council&#8217;s Plate trophy for six-a-side football. They never gave up drawing for most of the games  but towards the end starting winning games. They won 5 - 0 in the semi finals against Southampton City and in the final won 1-0 against Petersfield,  Petersfield was Baughurst Cub Scout&#8217;s hardest game, towards the end even Petersfield&#8217;s goal keeper came forward to try to score a goal. What impressed me the most was the cubs team work, decision making and changing tactics. It was great seeing a small rural group winning against much larger districts.&#8221;</p>

<p>The second email from one of the parents “the day was priceless, what a great bunch of kids they are,  a real credit to you (Cub Scout Leaders)”</p>

<p>The cubs were still on a high when we met for the last pack meeting of the term. Of the cubs that played at both competitions 7 are due to move up to Scouts over the course of this year so this has been a fantastic end to their time at cubs.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
